{
	"data": [
        {
            "question": "In a fortnight's time we ___ (take) our exam.",
            "answer": "will have taken",
            "explain": "Future perfect: \"will have taken\"\n+ Expresses the idea that something will occur before another action in the future. It can also show that something will happen before a specific time in the future\n+ Structure: S+ will/shall +have+PP\n+ Sign word: in fortnight's time",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "4",
            "subcategorylv2": "5",
            "type": "4"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ___ (finish) this book by tomorrow evening.",
            "answer": "will have finished",
            "explain": "Future perfect: \"will have finished\"\n+ Expresses the idea that something will occur before another action in the future. It can also show that something will happen before a specific time in the future\n+ Structure: S+ will/shall +have+PP\n+ Sign word: by tomorrow evening",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "4",
            "subcategorylv2": "5",
            "type": "4"
        },
        {
            "question": "By this time tomorrow we ___ (have) our injections.",
            "answer": "will have had",
            "explain": "Future perfect: \"will have had\"\n+ Expresses the idea that something will occur before another action in the future. It can also show that something will happen before a specific time in the future\n+ Structure: S+ will/shall +have+PP\n+ Sign word: by this time tomorrow",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "4",
            "subcategorylv2": "5",
            "type": "4"
        },
        {
            "question": "By the end of next year I ___ (be) here twenty-five years.",
            "answer": "will have been",
            "explain": "Future perfect: \"will have been\"\n+ Expresses the idea that something will occur before another action in the future. It can also show that something will happen before a specific time in the future\n+ Structure: S+ will/shall +have+PP\n+ Sign word: by the end of next year",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "4",
            "subcategorylv2": "5",
            "type": "4"
        },
        {
            "question": "I'll still be here next summer but Tom ___ (leave).",
            "answer": "will have left",
            "explain": "Future perfect: \"will have left\"\n+ Expresses the idea that something will occur before another action in the future. It can also show that something will happen before a specific time in the future\n+ Structure: S+ will/shall +have+PP\n+ Sign word: (by the time) next summer",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "4",
            "subcategorylv2": "5",
            "type": "4"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ___ (finish) this job in twenty minutes.",
            "answer": "will have finished",
            "explain": "Future perfect: \"will have finished\"\n+ Expresses the idea that something will occur before another action in the future. It can also show that something will happen before a specific time in the future\n+ Structure: S+ will/shall +have+PP\n+ Sign word: in twenty minutes",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "4",
            "subcategorylv2": "5",
            "type": "4"
        },
        {
            "question": "By next winter they ___ (build) four houses in that field.",
            "answer": "will have built",
            "explain": "Future perfect: \"will have built\"\n+ Expresses the idea that something will occur before another action in the future. It can also show that something will happen before a specific time in the future\n+ Structure: S+ will/shall +have+PP\n+ Sign word: by next winter\n\n",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "4",
            "subcategorylv2": "5",
            "type": "4"
        },
        {
            "question": "When we reach Valparaiso we ___ (sail) all round the world.",
            "answer": "will have sailed",
            "explain": "Future perfect: \"will have sailed\"\n+ Expresses the idea that something will occur before another action in the future. It can also show that something will happen before a specific time in the future\n+ Structure: S+ will/shall +have+PP\n+ Sign word: when we reach Valparaiso (imply that by the time we are at Valparaiso)",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "4",
            "subcategorylv2": "5",
            "type": "4"
        },
        {
            "question": "At the rate he is going he ___ (spend) all his money by the time he is twenty-one.",
            "answer": "will have spent",
            "explain": "Future perfect: \"will have spent\"\n+ Expresses the idea that something will occur before another action in the future. It can also show that something will happen before a specific time in the future\n+ Structure: S+ will/shall +have+PP\n+ Sign word: by the time\n",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "4",
            "subcategorylv2": "5",
            "type": "4"
        },
        {
            "question": "By this time next year I ___ (save) Â£250.",
            "answer": "will have saved",
            "explain": "Future perfect:  \"will have saved\"",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "4",
            "subcategorylv2": "5",
            "type": "4"
        }
    ]
}